Finding Aid for the Miriam Matthews photograph collection, 1781-1989 LSC.1889
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Prominent Individuals and Families., 1885-1980.
  - Danley/Johnson/Saunders families.
    - William and Hester Huston Saunders. (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Great grandparents of Theresa Harper Danley, individual portraits.
    - Samuel and Theresa Harper Danley. (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Family portraits of Theresa Harper and Samuel with two daughters, Samuel's graduation, Theresa's childhood.
    - Rory Boboa Lewis. (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Grandson of Mr. and Mrs. Samuel Danley, graduate of University of Alabama.
  - Ivan Johnson family.
    - Eugene Johnson and wife. (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Parents of Evelyn Harris
    - Daisy Johnson., undated. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dorothy Vena and Ivan Johnson. (Box 8, Folder 10)
      Ivan was an attorney, Dorothy, a teacher in Los Angeles city schools and president of Allied Arts League.
  - W.E.B. Du Bois.
    - W.E.B. Du Bois, scholar and civil rights activist., b. 1868- d. 1963. (Box 8, Folder 11)
      Portraits of Du Bois
  - Willis Duffy.
    - Willis Duffy and family. (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Negative family portrait Willis Duffy, wife, and three children.
  - George T. Dunlap.
    - George T. Dunlap, sister, and son-in-law. (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Includes photograph of George T. Dunlap and his son-in-law Truck Wilcox (August 1974) and Dunlap's sister in the 1890s
  - William E. Easton.
    - William E. Easton and family. (Box 8, Folder 14)
      Includes photographs of William Easton Sr. with his son William Easton Jr., and of Easton Sr. with his daughter Dorothy E. Houston and granddaughter Athenaise Houston.
  - Allen E. Flowers.
    - Allen E. Flowers and family. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Roy Fowler.
    - Roy Fowler, son of John Fowler., died 1919. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dunbar family.
    - Mr. and Mrs. A. Dunbar, at their farm in Inglewood. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Garrott/De Jarnette families.
    - Lydia De Jarnette (later married Alva C. Garrott) and her family. (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes photographs of Lydia (Lily), sister Alice De Jarnette Hooper, mother Mrs. Robert De Jarnette, and a family portrait.
    - Dr. A.C. Garrott and family. (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Portraits of Alva Curtis Garrott, including those with wife and children, and photographs of their house in Glendale.
    - Garrott family recreation. (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Includes photographs of Dr. A.C. Garrott and family members at picnics, in the park, playing tennis, and at Catalina Island. Many photographs of children.
    - Garrott family, 1950s. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes A.C Garrott and Robert Garrott.
    - Dr. Alice Watkins Garrott and family. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Graduate of Howard University dental school.
    - James Garrott, architect, and family. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Charlie Gibson.
    - Charlie Gibson as a child. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Hugh Gordon.
    - Hugh Gordon, businessman. (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Hugh Gordon was the originator of the Pyramid Cooperative Grocery and Meat Market. The Hugh Gordon bookshop near 45th street on Central Avenue was named for him
  - Berthella Glenn.
    - Berthella Glenn. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mabel Gray.
    - Mabel Gray, women's club leader. (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Portraits of Mabel Gray and photographs of her with various women's clubs
  - Grubbs family.
    - Grubbs family. (Box 9, Folder 11)
      Includes portraits of Fannie Ray, Alma, and Grace Grubbs
  - Harvey family.
    - Harvey family, contractors. (Box 9, Folder 12)
      Harvey brothers: Jesse, Ernest, and Frank. Sister Ruby Harvey. Brother-in-law Richard Foulkes. Father James Marsh Harvey, founder of Harvey Brothers Sand and Gravel contractors.
  - Hester family.
    - Norris and Marguerite Hester, children. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hewitt family.
    - Mrs. John Hewitt (Vennda Rei McFarlin). (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Betty Hill.
    - Betty Hill, civil rights activist. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Portraits of Betty Hill and photos of dedication of Will Rogers Park and swimming pool in appreciation of Hill.
  - Nan Holt.
    - Nan Holt, residence. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      1320 Albany St., Los Angeles
  - Houston family.
    - Edward Ross Houston. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Father of Athenaise Houston Hill and Millie Houston Price
  - Ida Jackson.
    - Ida Jackson. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Fay Jackson.
    - Faye Jackson. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Arthur Jenkins.
    - Aaron Arthur Jenkins. (Box 10, Folder 7)
      Includes Aaron Arthur Jenkins as an infant, his family including wife and children c. 1930, and his son George in the U.S. Army during WWII
  - Ivan J. Johnson.
    - Ivan J. Johnson collection. (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Identified and unidentified relatives of Ivan J. Johnson
    - Emma Gaines (Ivan Johnson's grandmother) and Ethel Mae Greer (Ivan's first cousin) on embroidered frame. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Theodore Johnson. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Clarence Jones.
    - Clarence Jones. (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Family wedding photo Dr and Mrs. John Simmons
  - Sarah Mildred Jones.
    - Sarah Mildred Jones., 1880s. (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Portrait of Sarah Jones, petition from teachers in Sacramento schools against her removal from Board of Education, negative of her students.
  - Lavon Julian.
    - Dr. Percy Lavon Julian, chemist, and family. (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Family portraits
  - Ballinger Kemp.
    - Ballinger Kemp. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Kenner family.
    - Byron and Louise Kenner, and relatives. (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Individual portraits, Byron and Louise at Bruce's Beach, Byron's retirement party,
  - Kimbrough family.
    - Jack Kimbrough's grandmother. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pocahontas O. Whiteman Key.
    - Pocahontas O. Whiteman Key. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Ellis Knox.
    - Ellis Knox, first African American to receive a PhD on the West Coast. (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Yearbook graduation page, A.B., California
  - Mary Ann Knox family.
    - Relatives of Mary Ann Knox. (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Photocopied copies of family photographs.
  - Leggett family.
    - Dr. and Mrs. James Leggett and daughter. (Box 10, Folder 20)
      Portrait in front of home on Ceres Ave. 1900
  - Lockett family.
    - James and Fannie Lockett., c. 1910. (Box 10, Folder 21)
      General store built and operated by Lockett family, Jennie Lockett (early California club woman), house in Duarte, (Photographs given by granddaughter Mabel Lockett Martin)
  - Luke family.
    - Sherrill and Anne Luke at their wedding (negative). (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Monroe Majors.
    - Dr. and Mrs. Monroe Majors (negative). (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Vivian Osborne Marsh family.
    - Vivian Osborne Marsh, community activist. (Box 10, Folder 24)
      Individual portraits
    - Vivian Osborne Marsh, community activities. (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Marsh at social events, club meetings, community events.
    - Relatives of Vivian Osborne and her youth. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Relatives of Leon Marsh. (Box 10, Folder 27)
      For negatives of Leon Marsh in the military, see box 19, folder 10.
  - Miriam Matthews family.
    - Portraits of friends to Matthews Family Binder. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Images taken from a binder compiled by Miriam Matthews, including snapshots and portraits of friends.
    - Photographs of friends and family of Miriam Matthews. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - McCard family.
    - McCard family. (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Includes Miriam McCard Rogers, Owen Johnson McCard, Beverly Scott McCard, and Lois McCard
  - Loren Miller family.
    - Loren Miller family. (Box 11, Folder 4)
      Includes some political photos taken by Harry H. Adams and a portrait of his wife Juanita Ellsworth Miller, a social worker. Many family photographs are unidentified
  - Lester Nicholas.
    - Lester Nicholas, child portrait. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Patterson family.
    - William and Louise Patterson with daughter Mary Lou. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - William Payne.
    - William Payne, portrait. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Pickens family.
    - Pickens Family. (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Includes Emilie Pickens' mother and father, Emilie Pickens and sons, William Pickens Jr., and William Pickens III. William Pickens was an orator and scholar and was active in the NAACP. Emilie Pickens was the founder of the Jack and Jill Organization in Brooklyn. All negatives.
  - James and Dorothy Porter.
    - James and Dorothy Porter, faculty of Howard University. (Box 11, Folder 9)
      Portrait of James as the head of the art gallery and art department at Howard University. Photographs of Dorothy receiving doctor of letters from Susquehanna University. Dorothy, a librarian, was instrumental in making the Moorland-Spingarn Research Center a premier research collection.
  - Emily Brown Childress Portwig and family.
    - Emily Brown Childress Portwig, pharmacist. (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Portraits, photograph with horse, and after graduating from USC with degree in pharmacy.
    - Emily and Rufus Portwig, and their residences. (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Includes country home at Val Verde, desert home in Victorville, and Los Angeles home
    - Party given by Emily Brown Childress (later Portwig) at her home., 1918. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Prince family.
    - Samuel Prince and family, Pasadena pioneers., b. 1844- d. 1907. (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Includes brothers Miller and James.
    - Arthur Prince. (Box 12, Folder 2)
      District Superintendent for Enterprise School District. Includes 1925 USC graduation photograph.
  - William Prince.
    - Rev. William Prince, second wedding. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      related to Samuel Prince family?
  - Francis Marion Ray.
    - Family of Francis Marion Ray., 1877-1951. (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Includes photographs c. 1877 of Francis Marion Ray, Lucinda Ray, Clarissa Reeves Ray. Class photograph from 1882 Sacramento school. Lucy Jane Ray (c. 1891), Mrs. Maud Ray Simons, George Ray, Nathan Ray, Charlie Ray, Clarissa Wildy, and Marion Wildy. See also Box 15, Folder 14.
  - Reddy family.
    - Mrs. Fred Reddy (nee: Marcia McFarlin). (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Negative
  - John Riddle.
    - John Riddle Sr. and Jr., 1925. (Box 12, Folder 6)
      Photograph of John Riddle Sr. on USC football team (1925), and his son John Riddle Jr., artist and art curator, with family.
  - Roberts/Hinds families.
    - "Roberts and Hinds Families" Binder. (Box 12, Folder 7)
      Photographs of Frederick Roberts and Pearl Hinds families, from a binder compiled by Miriam Matthews
    - Frederick Madison Roberts, newspaper owner and editor and California State Assemblyman. (Box 12, Folder 8)
      Individual portraits of Frederick Roberts from youth to adulthood.
    - Andrew J. Roberts and family. (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Andrew Roberts, sons Frederick and William, and daughter Essie
    - A.J. Roberts and Sons Funeral Home. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Gloria Roberts, daughter of Frederick Madison Roberts. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Dedication of Frederick Roberts Park in his honor. (Box 12, Folder 12)
      His wife receives key to the park
    - Unidentified Roberts family. (Box 12, Folder 13)
      Photographs of adults and children.
    - Pearl Hinds (later married Frederick Roberts). (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Includes school and graduation portraits, bridal portrait, and community involvement.
    - Wiley Hinds and wife (parents of Pearl Hinds). (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Children of Wiley Hinds. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Charlemae Hill Rollins.
    - Charlemae Hill Rollins, librarian., b. 1897- d. 1979. (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Description from Miriam Matthews "Distinguished librarian, noted author, dedicated humanitarian, crusader against stereotypes.
  - John Winiford Rout.
    - John Winiford Rout., 1924. (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Graduation photograph
  - Mattie Scott Nelson.
    - Mattie Scott Nelson and family. (Box 13, Folder 6)
      Scott family at home on San Julian St., Los Angeles. Mattie Scott Nelson's sister and her husband. Related to Lora Toombs Scott family.
  - John and Margaret Scott.
    - John and Margaret Scott, portraits as young people., undated. (Box 13, Folder 7)
      Owners of Scott's hall, civic leaders, pioneer members of First A.M.E. Church.
    - Margaret Scott., b. 1862- d. 1969. (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Includes individual portraits and a photograph of Margaret at the Sojourner Truth clubhouse, of which she was a co-founder in 1904.
    - John and Margaret Scott, business and residential properties., 1905- ?. (Box 13, Folder 9)
      Includes photographs of Scott's Hall
    - Margaret Scott as a centenarian., 1965-1967. (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Photographs of Margaret Scott on her 103rd, 104th, and 105th birthdays.
    - Margaret Scott Memorial tea., 1969. (Box 13, Folder 11)
      Held at Sojourner Truth Clubhouse. Photograph of group holding Margaret's portrait.
  - Lora Toombs Scott family.
    - Lora Toombs Scott, portrait., b. 1895. (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Born and raised in Northern California. A 1978 oral history interview of Scott can be found at www.archive.org.
    - Relatives of Lora Toombs Scott., 1800s. (Box 13, Folder 13)
      William and Minerva Robinson (grandparents), Pauline Logan, James Logan, Thomas Logan, Clara Logan Frazier (aunt), and other Logan family members.
    - Lora Toombs Scott's relatives (negatives). (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Leslie Shaw.
    - Leslie Shaw, first black postmaster in Los Angeles, and his wife Ann. (Box 13, Folder 15)
      Portrait of Ann and photograph of Leslie being sworn in as postmaster.
  - Skanks family.
    - Family of J.H. Skanks, barber. (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Includes photograph of Skanks family residence, Mrs. Skanks entertaining in her home, a portrait of five generations of women in the family, and Eva Allensworth Skanks who married Harrie Skanks. For more on Allensworth family see Box 5 Folder 5.
    - Margaret Smart., undated. (Box 13, Folder 17)
      Portrait of young woman
  - Nolle Smith.
    - Nolle Smith, businessman and diplomat in Hawaii., 1938. (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Photograph of Smith returning home to Honolulu after a trip to Los Angeles. Signed to Charles and Clarissa, "After a wonderful Summer, 1938, Nolle"
  - John and Vada Somerville family.
    - Dr. John Somerville, dentist and civic leader., b. 1882- d. 1973. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      Portraits of John Somerville, born in Jamaica and first black graduate of USC School of Dentistry (1907). He also built the Somerville Hotel (1928), was instrumental in the founding of the Los Angeles chapter of NAACP (1914), and served on the Police Commission 1949-1953.
    - Dr. Vada Somerville, dentist. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      Vada Somerville (born Vada Watson) of Pomona also graduated from USC in dentistry (1918) and entered into the practice with her husband John Somerville. She was highly involved in several civic and community organizations.
    - John and Vada Somerville, couple and anniversary photographs. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Includes photographs of 35th anniversary, 50th anniversary, and as a young married couple.
    - Vada Watson family. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Vada Watson's mother and brothers Welcome and John Emmanuel Watson
    - Somerville residences. (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Includes homes on S. Harvard Blvd., Virginia Rd., and an unidentified location.
    - Somerville Hotel., 1928. (Box 14, Folder 6)
      First opened in 1928, includes photographs of exterior and interior of hotel owned by John and Vada Somerville.
    - Hotel Somerville, ground-breaking., 1928. (Box 14, Folder 7)
      John and Vada Somerville, along with supporters, at ground-breaking for hotel
    - La Vada Apartments. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Property owned by Somervilles
    - Photo prints of documents relating to Somervilles. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      Emigration permit for John Somerville from Jamaica to California (1902), honorary Doctor of Laws from Bethune-Cookman College, honorary officer of British Order from Queen Elizabeth, certificate of honor for John and Vada on their 50th anniversary
    - Somerville community activities (1). (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Includes photographs of John and Vada's involvement in community service, fraternal organizations, clubs, and civil rights organizations.
    - Somerville community activities (2). (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Reception for Mr. and Mrs. R.C. Somerville of Linstead, Jamaica. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Vada Somerville hosts Eleanor Roosevelt. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - John Somerville as candidate for L.A. City Council and founding member of NAACP. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - John Somerville and Police Commissioner and receiving Order of the British Empire. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Friends and relatives of Somervilles. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Stephens and family.
    - Virginia Stephens, first black female lawyer in California, as a child in school. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Includes photograph on a tricycle, class photo at an Oakland elementary school (1914), class photo at Standard School in Monterey County, yearbook page from High School senior yearbook.
    - Virginia Stephens, as young adult. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Includes yearbook page as University of California graduate, photograph of Virginia attending a wedding, and group photo of a sorority (AKA?)
    - Portraits of Virginia Stephens, as adult. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Stephens Restaurant, Oakland CA. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Includes exterior and interior views.
    - William and Pauline Stephens, parents of Virginia. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Includes portraits from their marriage to middle-age. Mother, Pauline Stephens can also be found in box 13 folder 13 under her maiden name Pauline Logan. Also included is a portrait of Grace Logan Blick, sister of Pauline Stephens.
    - Relatives and friends of Virginia Stephens. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Includes grandmother, Annie Flood, and an unidentified actress.
    - Virginia Stephens' admission to practice law., 1929. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Ruth Temple.
    - Dr. Ruth Temple, physician and community health advocate. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      In 1918 Temple was the first black female graduate of Loma Linda University, and shortly after she began opening up health clinics providing free medical services and education. Later she was on the teaching staff of White Memorial hospital in Los Angeles.
  - James Monroe Vena family.
    - James Monroe Vena family. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Portraits of James Vena, his wife, his son James Monroe Vena Jr., daughters Dorothy and Yvonne. Also includes print of a page from the Liberator of James Vena as secretary of the Business Men's Association, 1904, and negative of James Vena with a survey team on the Los Angeles Plaza in the 1890s. Portrait of Cyrus Vena, father of James Vena. From collection of Los Angeles Public School teacher Dorothy Vena Johnson (who married Ivan J. Johnson, see box 10, folders 8-10.)
  - Mrs. Wade and daughter.
    - Mrs. Wade and daughter. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Photo by A.C. Garrott, no other identification.
  - Waugh, Cushnie families.
    - Waugh - Cushnie Family., c. 1906- 1918. (Box 15, Folder 11)
      Henry Clay Waugh; son Felix Hancock Waugh and his wife Mamie Lovett (Waugh); Mamie's mother Frances Merriweather Lovett; George and Amy O'Graffie Cushnie with oldest child Eugenia Cushnie Mason; and an unidentified man.
  - Fred Roscoe Whiteman.
    - Dr. Fred Roscoe Whiteman, physician and Army captain., c. 1943. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      Photograph of Whiteman has captain of 7th Regiment, Camp Temescal in Corona, CA; another photograph of Whiteman with his car.
  - Wickliffe family.
    - Minnie and Gustave Wickliffe family. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Includes portrait of Minnie Wickliffe as graduate of Oberlin. She was also a charter member of the first graduate chapter of the Alpha Kappa Alpha sorority in Los Angeles, 1927. Also included is a family portrait of Minnie, Gustave and children.
  - Clarissa Wildy family.
    - Clarissa Wildy and family photo album., c. 1891. (Box 15, Folder 14)
      Includes portrait of Clarissa Wildy, her mother Lucy Jane Ray, Marion Edwin Wildy, and a family portrait of David and Lucy Ray Hundley with their three nieces. Others secured from Lucy Jane Ray's photo album include: a portrait of Mr. and Mrs. Owen (nee: Mabelle Hutton), and a young girl with a doll on the porch to her home in Oakland, 1913. Also, see Box 12, Folder 4 for more on this family.
  - Charles E. Williams.
    - Charles E. Williams Sr. (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Dr. Williams was a leading member of the National Dental Association, an African American organization, and trained many African American dental technicians.
  - John W. Williams family.
    - Wife, daughters, granddaughters, great-grandson of John W. Williams. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      A photograph of four generations: Mrs. Williams (his wife), Mrs. Bessie Williams Dones (daughter), Mrs. Sylvetta B. Smith (granddaughter), and Pete Smith (great-grandson).
  - Small Portraits and Snapshots.
    - Small portraits and snapshots of African American families. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Includes Lois Towns Solomon, Helena Hester Harper, Mrs. Mitchell, group portrait of University Singers of New Orleans and several unidentified. Many appear to be family or friends of Lois Towns Solomon.
    - Framed portraits of African American leaders in Los Angeles. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Includes Betty Hill, Frederick Roberts, and Dorothy Vena Johnson. Also includes photograph of the Tyler residence.
  - Prints of pages from African American periodicals.
    - Prominent Individuals featured in African American Periodicals. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Periodicals include John Fowler's Spreading Joy c.1890s, California Negro Directory 1942-1943, the Los Angeles Sentinel, and one unidentified.
  - Unidentified Portraits.
    - Female members of same family?.
      Matthews grouped these unidentified portraits together; perhaps they are from the same family.
    - Unidentified group. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      These unidentified photographs were also grouped together by Miriam Matthews.
  - William A. Easter.
    - William A. Easter. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - George Wilson.
    - George Wilson. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Past grandmaster, past patron, Martha Chapter #6. From collection of Vivian Marsh.
  - Kate Sanderson Degrasse.
    - Kate Sanderson Degrasse. (Box 16, Folder 8)
      granddaughter of Rev. Sanderson. See box 19, folder 4.
  - Kate Bradley Stovall.
    - Kate Bradley Stovall, founder of Southern California Alumni Association. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Unidentified individuals and groups.
    - Unidentified individuals and groups (1 of 2). (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Includes photographs unidentified by Miriam Matthews.
    - Unidentified individuals and groups (2 of 2). (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Leroy Weekes.
    - Leroy Weekes, physician and community leader. (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Includes portrait of Weekes, obstetrician, president of the Urban League, and business leader.
  - Cushnie family.
    - Cushnie family. (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Includes unidentified photographs found in an envelope labeled, Cushnie.
  - Hugh and Ruth Bell.
    - Hugh and Ruth Bell at their wedding. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Included in portrait: Juanita Ellsworth, Ella Matthews, Edythe Pryce, and Alma Thomas.
  - M. I. Flood.
    - M. I. Flood (female). (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Frances Ford.
    - Frances Ford (female). (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Danley/McCard families
    - Danley/McCard families (Box 98, Folder 8-12)